const questions = [
  {
    question: "to take walk, to stroll",
    answer: "sanposuru",
    display: "さんぽする",
  },
  {
    question: "to close (something)",
    answer: "shimeru",
    display: "しめる",
  },
  {
    question: "to take out, to let out",
    answer: "dasu",
    display: "だす",
  },
  {
    question: "to go out",
    answer: "dekakeru",
    display: "でかける",
  },
  {
    question: "to help, to lend a hand",
    answer: "tetsudau",
    display: "てつだう",
  },
  {
    question: "to learn (with someone)",
    answer: "narau",
    display: "ならう",
  },
  {
    question: "to receive",
    answer: "morau",
    display: "もらう",
  },
  {
    question: "to forget",
    answer: "wasureru",
    display: "わすれる",
  },
  {
    question: "to give (to me)",
    answer: "kureru",
    display: "くれる",
  },
  {
    question: "to take (shower, sunbath)",
    answer: "abiru",
    display: "あびる",
  },
  {
    question: "to guide",
    answer: "annaisuro",
    display: "あんないする",
  },
  {
    question: "to hurry up",
    answer: "isogu",
    display: "いそぐ",
  },
  {
    question: "to drive",
    answer: "untensuru",
    display: "うんてんする",
  },
  {
    question: "to push, to press",
    answer: "osu",
    display: "おす",
  },
  {
    question: "to remember",
    answer: "omoidasu",
    display: "おもいだす",
  },
  {
    question: "to finish",
    answer: "owaru",
    display: "おわる",
  },
  {
    question: "to cose, to take (time)",
    answer: "kakaru",
    display: "かかる",
  },
  {
    question: "to marry",
    answer: "ketsukonsuru",
    display: "けつこんする",
  },
  {
    question: "to worry",
    answer: "shinpaisuru",
    display: "しんぱいする",
  },
  {
    question: "to throw away, to abandon",
    answer: "suteru",
    display: "すてる",
  },
  {
    question: "to sit down",
    answer: "suwaru",
    display: "すわる",
  },
  {
    question: "to explain",
    answer: "setsumeisuru",
    display: "せつめいする",
  },
  {
    question: "to stand up",
    answer: "tatsu",
    display: "たつ",
  },
  {
    question: "to get tired",
    answer: "tsukareru",
    display: "つかれる",
  },
  {
    question: "to be able, can",
    answer: "dekiru",
    display: "できる",
  },
  {
    question: "to call on the telephone",
    answer: "denwawokakeru",
    display: "でんわをかける",
  },
  {
    question: "to  lose",
    answer: "nakusu",
    display: "なくす",
  },
  {
    question: "to take off",
    answer: "nugu",
    display: "ぬぐ",
  },
  {
    question: "to climb",
    answer: "noboru",
    display: "のぼる",
  },
  {
    question: "to pull",
    answer: "hiku",
    display: "ひく",
  },
  {
    question: "to call",
    answer: "yobu",
    display: "よぼ",
  },
  {
    question: "to give back, to return",
    answer: "kaesu",
    display: "かえす",
  },
  {
    question: "to show",
    answer: "miseru",
    display: "みせる",
  },
  {
    question: "to need",
    answer: "iru",
    display: "いる",
  },
  {
    question: "to prepare",
    answer: "jyunbisuru",
    display: "じゅんびする",
  },
  {
    question: "to win",
    answer: "katsu",
    display: "かつ",
  },
  {
    question: "to endeavor, to do one's best",
    answer: "ganbaru",
    display: "がんばる",
  },
  {
    question: "to be able to",
    answer: "dekiru",
    display: "できる",
  },
  {
    question: "to lose (a game)",
    answer: "ma-ke-ru",
    display: "まける",
  },
  {
    question: "to start",
    answer: "hajimeru",
    display: "はじめる",
  },
  {
    question: "to change",
    answer: "kaeru",
    display: "かえる",
  },
  {
    question: "to be enough",
    answer: "tariru",
    display: "たりる",
  },
  {
    question: "to arrive",
    answer: "tsuku",
    display: "つく",
  },
  {
    question: "to take (someone)",
    answer: "tsureteiku",
    display: "つれていく",
  },
  {
    question: "to bring (someone)",
    answer: "tsuretekuru",
    display: "つれてくる",
  },
  {
    question: "to stop",
    answer: "tomeru",
    display: "とめる",
  },
  {
    question: "to become",
    answer: "naru",
    display: "なる",
  },
  {
    question: "to start, to begin",
    answer: "hajimaru",
    display: "はじまる",
  },
  {
    question: "to play (piano, guitar)",
    answer: "hiku",
    display: "ひく",
  },
  {
    question: "to fall (rain, snow)",
    answer: "furu",
    display: "ふる",
  },
  {
    question: "to carry",
    answer: "motsuteiku",
    display: "もつていく",
  },
];

export default questions;
